sidify.com 2018-06-29

# Sidify Privacy Policy

Sidify is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to Sidify's commitment to protecting your privacy. Sidify will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever. 

**What information do we collect? What do we use it for?**

When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you. 

**How do the 3rd party credit card processors protect customer's information?**

Sidify uses secure server hosted by 2CHECKOUT and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us, including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition. 

**2CHECKOUT**

2CHECKOUT is the leading digital commerce solution trusted by software and online services companies to grow their businesses globally. Sidify uses 2CHECKOUT to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase. 

**Contact information**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or programs of Sidify, please send email to our support: **support@sidify.com**
